I'm home!
Congratulations!
Thank you!
Oh no, I've triangulated!
We are almost at Maeyama!
So we've arrived at Maeyama!
Look at this!
We are reaching Maeyama!
Congratulations!
Thank you very much.
Are you okay?
We're reaching the front of the mountain.
Congratulations!
Welcome to Qianshan County.
I embrace you.
We're evacuating.
How's it going?
Dynamic Stage
Dynamic stage
Really.
Dynamic stage.
I'm going to be invited on stage.
We just went on stage.
Two hands on stage.
What do you mean?
One row?
Maybe two.
Okay, two.
We need to get as close to the front as possible.
If we don't pack it in as tight as possible, Ao-Mi-An will die.
Yay!
That's great.
The floor is all up on Mikio's slope.
The floor is amazing!
MIKIO SAKA
If you look at it as a slope...
Kasaki Hyuga
Hinata Hinata
No, it's not.
Do I look like Hinata?
Your eyebrows are thicker.
You're a great loser.
Nice.
Hinata's a loser.
You have leaves all around you.
It's like that.
Boku boku boku.
But I went to bed without salt, so I didn't eat any.
Didn't you have a snack earlier?
276 calories.
That's a lot.
It's just my feet.
You're still a little girl, aren't you?
I feel sorry for you right away.
I'll feel sorry for you in a minute.
Right away, sir.
He's trying to stir things up.
Maybe he's trying to stir things up.
Oh, no.
Oh, poor baby.
Oh, my God.
His reaction today...
Aorigaru!
They all have a motif.
There's a big theme today.
what is it?
Please listen to the aorigaru.
Let's see...
Seafood!
It's stopped!
What is it?
It's okay.
First...
Four.
The last one.
Five.
Correct answer is
Giana
Excel
You're definitely a pussy.
I'm not...
You're not a pussy.
I'm not a pussy.
I'm not a punchline.
I'm sweet and sour. It's amazing.
I'm sweet.
It's really elaborate.
Looks delicious.
I'm going to go with scallops.
Gari to scallops.
I was shocked.
It's like Mirin-san.
Smooth
Was it scalloped gari
Manju-gari
Min-chan's face is manju
He said that
I didn't go that far.
Min-chan, your face is manjuu.
Risa-chan...
Paco.
But for a moment
Eh, a moment
Whoo-hoo!
That's the smell of Buffoon.
That's it... the smell of Buffoon.
Oh, luxury.
Tips.
It's wakame.
Not kelp.
It's more like wakame.
It's thick soup stock.
The long kind you use for soup stock.
There's only one.
Yes, I've only got one hit.
Asari.
I remember.
I played an asari in kindergarten.
Asari Soup.
What play?
I don't know.
Risa-chan?
I don't think so.
Do it like this
How do you do it?
And there are 10 of them.
Yes, ten.
It's so elaborate.
I can't tear them off before I'm done.
Oh, no.
I'm going to tear them off.
There's only ten of them.
I'm gonna have to cover it up.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
Oh, no.
It's Blue.
He's here.
I'm from Toyonawan.
I'm a white shrimp.
Here.
Like this.
We eat here.
Here
Feel the sea
Feel
Tactile sensation
What's the pelorin?
that... that...whoa (used to express surprise or stupefaction)
tropical fish
Flander
Search for
Customer's store
Beautiful
Aimanin Marche is available for purchase
I was doing my hair.
I was getting my hair done and everyone in the dressing room was asking
They were asking me which line I wanted to use for Perrin.
What's that?
What? The line?
I don't know what's left.
I put a ponytail on it.
She said, "What line?
What line?
It's coming up.
When?
When do I go to him?
I don't know when to go to "yes, sir.
Two minutes ago, by the way.
Not two minutes ago.
But...
During the announcements.
We did it the other day, right?
Grandpa's.
It's definitely Grandpa's
Narrative.
Grandpa's
Grandpa's.
Maybe it's Grandpa's.
This is the first time the seven of us have performed together on
stage today.
But the stage itself is small, so
so please don't get hurt or anything.
Let's have fun and make it exciting.
Let's go!
Congratulations!
Thank you very much.
We're still going to continue with the start.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
I'm so glad that I could finally come on the line like this.
Anyway, the calls were great!
I hope we can all come back to Toyama again.
I'll do my best!
There are still 3days left in Hokuriku.
Blue Comet of Hokuriku
and the power of the radio wave group
I'll be showing you the power of the Hokuriku Blue Comet and the Radio Group more and more and more and more.
I hope all the Hokuriku players
and all the other players
I look forward to working with you.
Yosha!
Nemu-chan!
Hey, Nemu-chan!
I'm looking at you, Nemu.